export const Questions = [
  {
    question: "What is React?",
    options: ["Library", "Framework", "Language", "Database"],
    answer: "Library",
  },
  {
    question: "Which hook is used for state in functional components?",
    options: ["useEffect", "useState", "useReducer", "useContext"],
    answer: "useState",
  },
  {
    question: "Which company developed React?",
    options: ["Google", "Facebook", "Microsoft", "Netflix"],
    answer: "Facebook",
  },
  {
    question: "What does JSX stand for?",
    options: [
      "JavaScript XML",
      "Java Syntax eXtension",
      "JSON XML",
      "JavaScript eXtension",
    ],
    answer: "JavaScript XML",
  },
  {
    question: "Which prop is used to pass data to components?",
    options: ["props", "state", "data", "info"],
    answer: "props",
  },
  {
    question: "Which hook runs after every render?",
    options: ["useEffect", "useMemo", "useState", "useCallback"],
    answer: "useEffect",
  },
  {
    question: "How do you create a React app using Vite?",
    options: [
      "npx create-react-app",
      "npm create vite@latest",
      "npm react-create-app",
      "yarn vite-init",
    ],
    answer: "npm create vite@latest",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the default package manager for Node.js?",
    options: ["npm", "yarn", "pnpm", "bun"],
    answer: "npm",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these is a state management library?",
    options: ["Redux", "Tailwind", "React Router", "Vite"],
    answer: "Redux",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which attribute is used to specify a unique key for list items in React?",
    options: ["id", "key", "name", "index"],
    answer: "key",
  },
];
